# Hamilton Alvarez

City: Visalia, CA

Email: hamilton1226@outlook.com

**Phone:** 1-707-901-7859

## Summary Qualifications \_\_\_\_\_

Dedicated and efficient full stack developer with 6+ years experience in application layers, presentation layers, and databases.

Meticulous web developer with over 2 years of front end experience and passion for responsive website design.

Now, trying to further improve HTML5 and CSS3 skills as the future full stack developer at Atmospheric Solutions.

## Work Experience

## **Backend Developer**

Jun 2015 - Dec 2017

#### **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Implemented RESTful APIs to connect frontend applications with backend.
- Created unit tests and integration tests using Go, PHP and JavaScript for.
- Improved existing RESTful APIs by adding more functionality and error.

## **Full Stack Developer**

Apr 2013 - Mar 2015

#### **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Built several backend platform using Node.js.
- Developed front end application with Vue and React.
- Manipulated data using CRUD operations of MS SQL Server and handled.
- Structured and clear vision of your future application.
- Communication was held through our Slack channel

## **Full Stack Developer**

May 2016-June 2019

General Gaming, Boston, MA

#### **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Developed full-stack web applications which processed, analyzed, and rendered data visually.
- Managed time-sensitive updates, including content changes and database upgrades.
- Planned, wrote, and debugged web applications and software with complete accuracy.

# Key Skills\_\_\_\_\_

- Web Development Stacks (Mern)
- Database Technology (MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB)
- ➤ HTML & CSS
- JavaScript & JS Frameworks (Angular JS, React, Vue)
- Basic UI/UX Design
- ➤ Node.is
- > Python
- Django
- > PHP

# **Education**

Keio University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (April 2009 - February 2013)

**Relevant Coursework**: Operating Systems Architecture, Linux/Unix Programming, Usability in

Website and Software Design, Web Page Development, Relational Database Design & SQL, Data Engineering,

Advanced Software Programming.

## Language

> English